{
    "studyset": "33659919",
    "data": [
        {
            "question": "的 de",
            "answer": "of"
        },
        {
            "question": "一 yī",
            "answer": "one"
        },
        {
            "question": "是 shì",
            "answer": "to be"
        },
        {
            "question": "不 bù",
            "answer": "not"
        },
        {
            "question": "了 le",
            "answer": "completed"
        },
        {
            "question": "在 zài",
            "answer": "at / in"
        },
        {
            "question": "人 rén",
            "answer": "person"
        },
        {
            "question": "有 yǒu",
            "answer": "to have"
        },
        {
            "question": "我 wǒ",
            "answer": "I / me"
        },
        {
            "question": "他 tā",
            "answer": "he / him"
        },
        {
            "question": "这 zhè",
            "answer": "this"
        },
        {
            "question": "个 gè",
            "answer": "individual"
        },
        {
            "question": "中 zhōng",
            "answer": "middle"
        },
        {
            "question": "为 wèi",
            "answer": "for"
        },
        {
            "question": "大 dà",
            "answer": "big"
        },
        {
            "question": "们 men",
            "answer": "plural"
        },
        {
            "question": "来 lái",
            "answer": "come"
        },
        {
            "question": "上 shàng",
            "answer": "above / up"
        },
        {
            "question": "以 yǐ",
            "answer": "so as to"
        },
        {
            "question": "国 guó",
            "answer": "country"
        },
        {
            "question": "和 hé",
            "answer": "and / with"
        },
        {
            "question": "到 dào",
            "answer": "to arrive"
        },
        {
            "question": "地 dì",
            "answer": "earth"
        },
        {
            "question": "之 zhī",
            "answer": "of / it"
        },
        {
            "question": "说 shuō",
            "answer": "to say"
        },
        {
            "question": "时 shí",
            "answer": "time"
        },
        {
            "question": "要 yào",
            "answer": "want"
        },
        {
            "question": "出 chū",
            "answer": "out"
        },
        {
            "question": "也 yě",
            "answer": "also"
        },
        {
            "question": "就 jiù",
            "answer": "just"
        },
        {
            "question": "可 kě",
            "answer": "can"
        },
        {
            "question": "会 huì",
            "answer": "able to"
        },
        {
            "question": "而 ér",
            "answer": "yet / but"
        },
        {
            "question": "于 yú",
            "answer": "in / at / than"
        },
        {
            "question": "子 zǐ",
            "answer": "child"
        },
        {
            "question": "生 shēng",
            "answer": "life"
        },
        {
            "question": "对 duì",
            "answer": "correct"
        },
        {
            "question": "年 nián",
            "answer": "year"
        },
        {
            "question": "能 néng",
            "answer": "can"
        },
        {
            "question": "得 dé",
            "answer": "to get"
        },
        {
            "question": "你 nǐ",
            "answer": "you"
        },
        {
            "question": "下 xià",
            "answer": "down"
        },
        {
            "question": "自 zì",
            "answer": "self"
        },
        {
            "question": "道 dào",
            "answer": "way"
        },
        {
            "question": "那 nà",
            "answer": "that"
        },
        {
            "question": "后 hòu",
            "answer": "after"
        },
        {
            "question": "行 xíng",
            "answer": "to go/OK"
        },
        {
            "question": "着 zhe",
            "answer": "~ing"
        },
        {
            "question": "发 fā",
            "answer": "to send out"
        },
        {
            "question": "过 guò",
            "answer": "to pass"
        },
        {
            "question": "所 suǒ",
            "answer": "actually"
        },
        {
            "question": "用 yòng",
            "answer": "to use"
        },
        {
            "question": "作 zuò",
            "answer": "to do"
        },
        {
            "question": "事 shì",
            "answer": "matter/thing"
        },
        {
            "question": "家 jiā",
            "answer": "home"
        },
        {
            "question": "里 lǐ",
            "answer": "in/inside"
        },
        {
            "question": "成 chéng",
            "answer": "to become"
        },
        {
            "question": "方 fāng",
            "answer": "square"
        },
        {
            "question": "其 qí",
            "answer": "its"
        },
        {
            "question": "然 rán",
            "answer": "so"
        },
        {
            "question": "种 zhǒng",
            "answer": "type of"
        },
        {
            "question": "去 qù",
            "answer": "go"
        },
        {
            "question": "如 rú",
            "answer": "like/as"
        },
        {
            "question": "多 duō",
            "answer": "many/much"
        },
        {
            "question": "经 jīng",
            "answer": "to pass"
        },
        {
            "question": "法 fǎ",
            "answer": "law/method"
        },
        {
            "question": "学 xué",
            "answer": "to study"
        },
        {
            "question": "同 tóng",
            "answer": "same"
        },
        {
            "question": "天 tiān",
            "answer": "sky/day"
        },
        {
            "question": "都 dōu",
            "answer": "all"
        },
        {
            "question": "分 fēn",
            "answer": "to divide"
        },
        {
            "question": "当 dāng",
            "answer": "regard as"
        },
        {
            "question": "定 dìng",
            "answer": "to set"
        },
        {
            "question": "者 zhě",
            "answer": "one who (is)"
        },
        {
            "question": "进 jìn",
            "answer": "to enter"
        },
        {
            "question": "么 me",
            "answer": "suffix"
        },
        {
            "question": "十 shí",
            "answer": "ten"
        },
        {
            "question": "主 zhǔ",
            "answer": "main"
        },
        {
            "question": "日 rì",
            "answer": "sun/day"
        },
        {
            "question": "动 dòng",
            "answer": "to move"
        },
        {
            "question": "部 bù",
            "answer": "part"
        },
        {
            "question": "现 xiàn",
            "answer": "now"
        },
        {
            "question": "面 miàn",
            "answer": "face"
        },
        {
            "question": "起 qǐ",
            "answer": "to rise"
        },
        {
            "question": "小 xiǎo",
            "answer": "small"
        },
        {
            "question": "理 lǐ",
            "answer": "to manage"
        },
        {
            "question": "还 hái",
            "answer": "still"
        },
        {
            "question": "军 jūn",
            "answer": "army"
        },
        {
            "question": "与 yǔ",
            "answer": "and"
        },
        {
            "question": "看 kàn",
            "answer": "to see"
        },
        {
            "question": "本 běn",
            "answer": "origin"
        },
        {
            "question": "好 hǎo",
            "answer": "good"
        },
        {
            "question": "无 wú",
            "answer": "without"
        },
        {
            "question": "前 qián",
            "answer": "in front/ago"
        },
        {
            "question": "些 xiē",
            "answer": "some"
        },
        {
            "question": "没 méi",
            "answer": "haven't"
        },
        {
            "question": "心 xīn",
            "answer": "heart"
        },
        {
            "question": "因 yīn",
            "answer": "cause"
        },
        {
            "question": "从 cóng",
            "answer": "from"
        },
        {
            "question": "三 sān",
            "answer": "three"
        }
    ]
}
